The CUE event is an event that's held every year at Bodwell
CUEイベントは、Bodwellで毎年開催されるイベントです。
where 50 Canadian universities come to Bodwell to speak to our students
カナダの50大学の担当者がボドウェルに集まり
They have the opportunities to speak directly to admission reps from various universities
生徒達は、様々な大学の入学担当者と直接話す機会があります。
ask them questions about admission
入試についての質問や入学条件など
and admission requirements. We actually encourage grades 10 11 and 12 students to attend
ボドウェルでは高１～３までの生徒の参加を奨励しています
They can ask any question regarding
生徒達は色々な質問をすることができます
admission requirements everything from averages needed
a必要な成績や入学要件すべて
Courses that universities are looking for, supplementary applications, and other criterias that universities might be looking for
入学審査に有利な科目、追加書類、および大学が提示しているその他の基準
Since not all university requirements are the same
すべての大学の入学審査要件が、同じというわけではないので
it's imperative for students to talk to the admission officers
学生が入学担当官と話すことは、とても重要です
from various universities to ask them specific questions about their admission criteria and requirements
様々な大学へ、入学基準と要件について具体的な質問ができる
Bodwell hosts the CUE event to give our students opportunity to speak to those university reps in person
このCUEイベントを主催して、当校の学生に直接大学の担当者と話す機会を提供しています。
The next step for our students is to do a follow up with their counselors by sitting down with them
生徒達の次のステップは、カウンセラーとフォローアップをすることです。
They sit down with the counselors one-on-one after the event to discuss the various options
イベントの後、カウンセラーと一対一で座り、そして彼らがCUEイベントで学んだこと
and opportunities they have learned themselves at the CUE event
さまざまな選択肢について話し合います。
Rather than having our students miss school to go meet
50の大学へ訪問する為に、学校を休むのではなく
50 universities at 50 different locations
50大学の担当者が、ボドウェル高校
It's an opportunity for our students to have all 50 reps in one place and talk to them in person
1か所に集まる事で、生徒たちは直接、大学と話し合う機会があります。
They can also make personal connection with the University reps
生徒達は、大学の担当者と直接コンタクトをとれる関係を作ることもできます。
They will have their contact information and they will be able to contact them one-on-one in case they needed to
大学の担当者の連絡先をもらい、必要な場合には、直接連絡することができます。
Prior to attending this event
また、このイベントに参加する前に
students are encouraged in class,
生徒達は、事前に大学のリサーチをし
and through meeting with counsellors to ask specific questions to the University reps
カウンセラーとの面談を通じて、大学の担当者に具体的な質問を考えます。
Those questions are discussed in CLE  classes and when the students meet with their counsellors back again 1 on 1
これらの質問は、CLEというクラス内、またはカウンセラーとの話し合いの中でもアドバイスされます。